We just finished watching Seize for Liberation here at the People's Forum, and I'm telling you now, if you haven't watched it yet, go watch this film.
I mean, we're looking at organizers, we're hearing from activists, we're hearing from lawyers, we're hearing from people who understand the importance of solidarity between Palestinian liberation, evacuation, Chicano liberation, but it's a call to action.
And I think we're ready to get active.
What do you think?
I think what it really shows is that folks are active.
And so for those who are saying to themselves, like, man, I really need to get in this, you are not stepping into a new fight.
You know, you're joining a movement and an energy that is already moving and it is only getting stronger.
I love that this is a record of the now.
You know, we need to be keeping our own record of this history that is happening so quickly, right, so that we can also be able to identify the ways in which we can continue to get stronger.
And this shows that solidarity and getting out of our silos and working together is the way forward.
And so we just need to continue to do that.